Guide to the Kate Bornstein papers 1910-2018
Brown University Library
- Digital materials
  - 3-2 Borderline, Beta 1.pages
  - 3-2.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life - 2.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  - 3-4 Where It Gets Complicated V2.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st hackjob.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st merge.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated-tighter.pages
  - avb_obit.pages
  - eulogy for my brother.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5 - 2.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5 - 3.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5.pages
  - how the sea org made a man out of me.pages
  - text to grab for so made a man.pages
  - 3-1 Alpha Draft In Progress.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 1.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 1-5.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 2.pages
  - 3-5 Everybody Else's Girl Beta 1.0.pages
  - 3-5 Girl, After Hard Copy Edit Beta 2.0.pages
  - A Queer and Pleasant Mistress.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 kb pass 1.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 (original).pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 cleanstart.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2.pages
  - Book 2 Exported From Scrivener.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  - pages compatibility check kb pass 1.pages
  - 3-5 Girl KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.0.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.1.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 clean.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 3 for Scrivener.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 3 KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Part 3 Redux.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie—Gold.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 Gold.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 clean.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB pass 2.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  - book 1.pages
  - book 2.pages
  - book 3.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 3.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2 clean.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  - Text for Cover Proposal 2.pages
  - Text for Cover Proposal.pages
  - book-spine.pages
  - Queer Pleasant Book Cover Beta 1.pages
  - QueerPleasantBookCoverTextPush.pages
  - My Girlfriend Is Becoming The Man Of My Dreams.pages
  - Dixon Place QPD Launch Schedule.pages
  - DixonPlaceQPDlaunchFlier.pages
  - Kate Bornstein, Book Release Event-May 1st, 120406.pages
  - KBDixonPlaceLaunchPressRelease.pages
  - QueerAndPleasantLaunchProgram.pages
  - climbing the foremast.pages
  - Coming Out.pages
  - molly asks me to marry her.pages
  - My Virginity.pages
  - BILD Interview.pages
  - A Queer And Pleasant Danger Pre Copy Edit.pages
  - letter to jess.pages
  - cover letter to page proof corrections.pages
  - QPD Page Proof Attachments.pages
  - Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  - KB_AuthorPublicity&Marketing.pages
  - A Queer And Pleasant Danger.pages
  - QueerPleasantDanger1_5.pages
  - QueerPleasantDanger_1_5_illustrated.pages
  - Miss G monologue.pages
  - Virtually Yours 2.0.pages
  - Virtually Yours Intro, Beta 1.pages
  - Keynote Champaign-Urbana Pride Festival.pages
  - 3-4 Minutes 4th Annual Womens Awards.pages
  - For the Fun of It Intro 3.0.pages
  - The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  - You Me and Gender BC PASS.pages
  - 20 Questions.pages
  - DIVA questions Pages09.pages
  - Bornstein's Theory of Relativity KB pass Pages 09.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-1.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-2.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-3.pages
  - China Film Text 1st Draft P09.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Final.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote No Restrictions.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-2.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-3.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Sync.pages
  - Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum for blog.pages
  - Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum.pages
  - Play List for @largeheartedboy.pages
  - Power of Femme Marist Conf Keynote.pages
  - KB_OpEd_Aug2014_Pages_09.pages
  - KB_OpEd_Aug2014-2.pages
  - CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - KB final draft CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - Genesis Pomo.pages
  - Mitzvah Sabbath KESHET 09.pages
  - NUJLS Mitzvah Text.pages
  - Talk at Vigil Against Hate Crimes Xavier 09.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for Neherim.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for RRC 2012.pages
  - Welcome to NYU LGBTQ.pages
  - Description.pages
  - Supplies.pages
  - KB Photo Assortment 2011.pages
  - KB-Career-Summary-2010.pages
  - Author Questionnaire by Kate Bornstein.pages
  - B survey letter pages 09.pages
  - BC to Donia Finders Fees Smackdown.pages
  - Figments of Erotic Imagination-KB Pass.pages
  - New BDSM Chapter—KB Pass.pages
  - New EAM for T&GNC People Chapter KB pass.pages
  - New Introduction copy KB pass.pages
  - New Safer Sex section—KB PASS.pages
  - Orgasms with Spirit Class #4 KB Pass.pages
  - Trans Survey Draft #2 KB pass pages 09.pages
  - Urban Tantra certificate.pages
  - GSMS Foreword by BC—KB pass.pages
  - Chapt. #1-The Ecstatic Experience Vs2.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB 1st Draft.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better KB 2nd pass.pages
  - Rogue femininity.pages
  - Buffalo Night by Caitlin.pages
  - Midnight Bleary.pages
  - David Harrison My experiences on the CSETI Training.pages
  - femme on femme long version.pages
  - My White Underwear Story.pages
  - JVB Interview.pages
  - A.Mc.Q.201120.pages
  - Princess book proposal.pages
  - Princess Proposal 2.0.pages
  - Antig-Lines.pages
  - GoFundMe Comments.pages
  - Kate Stay Alive.pages
  - 17-18 Tour Catalogue.pages
  - Talking Points B's Ecstasy Hour.pages
  - short talk performance & workshop descriptions.pages
  - NYSAF.F TO M.Kate Bornstein (Dr. Shelton).pages
  - An addendum to house sit.pages
  - House-Sitter Factoids.pages
  - Quotes About KB.pages
  - 09-10 newsletter.pages
  - Kate Bornstein One Sheet.pages
  - 10-11 newsletter.pages
  - 13-14 newsletter.pages
  - catalogue essay 13-14.pages
  - some text for 13-14 cat.pages
  - MWRU Director Script La Mama 2017.pages
  - MWRU Performance Script 2016 PO9.pages
  - Backup of Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  - Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  - Talking Points Pre-Trans March.pages
  - 100 GLBT Colleges Contact Info.pages
  - FINAL Schedule for Kate Bornstein Visit.pages
  - New Gigs 09 outline.pages
  - KB_Amherst_Details.pages
  - ASU SORC Speaker Template.pages
  - Masque for John #1.pages
  - 09-106 LGBTA 2-11 Speaker.pages
  - kate's itinerary.pages
  - Power Bottoming panel at TES.pages
  - Appearance Agreement Kate Bornstein.pages
  - contract U Miss.pages
  - Kate Bornstein Contract.pages
  - KATE BORNSTEIN schedule.pages
  - Denver-Twin Cities.pages
  - Elon University 041112 itinerary.pages
  - final proposal.pages
  - IC_Kate Bornstein completed.pages
  - University of Toledo 10.16.13 schedule.pages
  - University of Illinois 100212 itinerary.pages
  - University of Florida 102212 itinerary.pages
  - Urbana Trip 0913-20 schedule.pages
  - Bornstein QAF contract 2012.pages
  - Bornstein Rider QAF 2012.pages
  - Kate Bornstein workshop contract.pages
  - WNE_KateB_itinerary.pages
  - KB_Acting_Wkshop_Handout.pages
  - KB-Acting-Wkshop-Handout-2.pages
  - charts for role play.pages
  - Guidepost & Control System Charts.pages
  - Michael Shurtleff 12 Guideposts.pages
  - 2012 Talk to CCSU 3rd Annual Lavender Commencement.pages
  - Carroll University NCOD 2010.pages
  - CBST Pride Shabat Talk.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 09.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 2013.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SASSE 2010.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SFU 09.pages
  - Hello Cruel Bullies ♀ History 2011.pages
  - KB CBST Pride Shabat 2012.pages
  - Men Women Rest of Us Perf Notes 2012.pages
  - Sex, Bullies, and You 2009.pages
  - Sex, Bullies, and You 2010 Reader.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  - Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  - william paterson piece.pages
  - Anna Story.pages
  - Politics of Desire 1.0.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - Theater, and Future of the Body.pages
  - Man Without a Family Reader.pages
  - Reading with David.pages
  - Carrol Univ Coming Out Day.pages
  - Hidden A Gender.pages
  - The Monologues.pages
  - 316 HouseSit Notes 1013.pages
  - 316 HouseSit Notes Apr2013 KB.pages
  - do u c p.pages
  - KB Books Amazon Links pages 09.pages
  - A Plan For Peace Nov 27 92.pages
  - aftercare.pages
  - Dear Galley Reader Letter.pages
  - dixon place femme blurb.pages
  - email from pussy.pages
  - KB long bio May 2015 pages09.pages
  - KB pass at TCKB.pages
  - KB Pass.pages
  - memoir-template.pages
  - Pioneer Speaking.pages
  - Questions_for_Switzerland BC Pass.pages
  - Timed Talk—Save This As Template.pages
  - A Plan For Peace Nov 27 92.pages
  - Apartheid of Sex Martine Rothblatt.pages
  - Talk to KC L&G re Brandon Teena May 14 1995.pages
  - An Afternoon of Bridge.pages
  - Backup of Two Forms of ID.pages
  - Circumstances by Design.pages
  - Face In The Mirror.pages
  - Newlyweds.pages
  - Team Spirit.pages
  - Testing a Theory.pages
  - Two Forms of ID.pages
  - 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC 6-11 Cape Cod.pages
  - 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC Aug2011.pages
  - ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  - Lock the DAMN door.pages
  - turn around damn door.pages
  - JJ_Reading.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic 2.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic.pages
  - Scientology New Yorker.pages
  - Scientology Nuts and Bolts.pages
  - call me a cockeyed optimist.pages
  - Chapter 3 Ebook.pages
  - Hard Candy Chapter 3 Reader.pages
- Biographical, 1910-2017
  - Astralogical charts, ca.2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards and honors, 1991-2014, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bios; includes bio packet prepared by Craig R. Dean from Outright Speakers and Talent Bureau, ca.1998, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Birth certificate, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings about Kate Bornstein (1 of 4), ca.1986-2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings about Kate Bornstein (2 of 4), ca.1986-2016 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings about Kate Bornstein (3 of 4), ca.1986-2016 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings about Kate Bornstein (4 of 4), ca.1986-2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Contacts: bound volume (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Contacts: business cards, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Divorce documents, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Drawings by Kate Bornstein (bound) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Drawings by Kate Bornstein (unbound) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Drawings of Kate Bornstein, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Driver's licenses and identification cards, ca.1990-2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Employment dispute file: Bornstein versus Satellite Business Systems re: Bornstein's transgenderism, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Genealogical file: adoption records re: Jessica Leah Bornstein [daughter]. Contains correspondence and legal documents re: Kate Bornstein's relinguishment of custody, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Genealogical file: birth certificate of Paul Bornstein [father], 1910 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (1 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (2 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (3 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (4 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (5 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (6 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (7 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (8 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook letters of Mildred Vandam [mother]. Contains letters from Paul Bornstein [father] to Mildred during Paul's service in Europe during World War II (9 of 9), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Genealogical file: scrapbook pages. Contains unbound scrapbook pages showing the receipt date and organization of related scarpbook letters., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Health files originally located in Box 1, Folders 29-33, are closed until January 1, 2039. [SEE RESTRICTED FOR NEW LOCATION], n.d.
  - Interview; contains questions and answers before publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Interview at New York University, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Interview in TransSisters: The Journal of Transsexual Feminism, Summer 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Interview in the Village Voice, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Juror questionnaire, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Membership file (general), 1994, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Membership file re: Feminists for Free Expression, ca.2005 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Membership file re: Transsexual Support Group of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Name-change decree of Albert Herman Bornstein to Katherine Vandam Bornstein, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Performance contracts, 1999-2007, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Performance file re: Ms. Leather Contest judged by Bornstein, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Performance flyers [selection only], 2002-2017, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Perfomrance/travel itineraries, 2000-2011, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Syllabi featuring Kate Bornstein (1 of 2), 1987-2015 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Syllabi featuring Kate Bornstein (2 of 2), 1987-2015 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Theatre programs: Brown University; includes Sock and Buskin programs featuring Al Bornstein. Also includes schedule sheet for the Alumni Caberet, 1966-1968, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Wedding event material re: Elizabeth M. Stephans and Annie Sprinkle [friends of Kate Bornstein and Barbara Carrellas] (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Yearbook: The Pennington School, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Yearbook: The Pennington School, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Yearbook: The Pennington School, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1977-2018
  - Correspondence; contains letter from a physician to a medical student re: affect of sex change surgury on ability to practice medicine, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence; includes letter to Andrea Dworkin from Lauren Wilson re: transsexual persons and pornography, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence; contains letter and flyers from transgender photographer, Loren Cameron, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence; includes letter from Hillary Clinton, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence; includes fan letters from transgender persons, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence; includes letters re: Bornstein's health and surgery, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence; includes letters from friends and family following publication of A Queer and Pleasant Danger. Also re: Bornstein's health, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence; incudes letters re: Bornstein's health, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Albert Bornstein and "Mom" [Mildred Vandam Bornstein] re: coming out as transgender, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from "Admiral" to "Starbuck", 2012, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Albert Bornstein to Brown University friend "Donna" re: coming out as transgender, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Albert Bornstein to daughter "Jessica" and ex-wife "Molly" re: being transgender, Scientology, and family relationships, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from Antioch University, Los Angeles re: Master of Fine Arts guest writer postion; includes reading packet, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from Barbara Carrellas; contains greeting cards, 2001, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from Bear Bergman (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Michelle Quintas, United Airlines flight attendant, on cocktail napkin (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from Virginia Ramey Mollenkott, 1999-2013 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re: Bornstein's employment; contains resumes, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence re: Hello Cruel World survey; contains questions and responses (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re: Hello Cruel World survey; contains questions and responses (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to "Auntie Kate", 2012 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Diaries and Notes, 1983-2015
  - Diary, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Diary, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Diary, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Diary, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Diary, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Diary, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Diary, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Diary, ca.2006 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Diary, ca.2006 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Diary, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Diary, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Diary, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Diary, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Diary; contains two volumes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Diary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "Notes to self", ca.2004-2014 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Notes to self", 2010, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Notes to self;" contains Post-Its, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "Notes to self;" contains Post-Its, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Conferences, 1991-2017
  - 1991 - Athe91 Conference; contains program (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1998 - Transpositions: A Conference Towards Transgender Studies; contains program (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1999 - Getting the Love You Want Couples Workshop; contains list of dates, manual, and completed worksheets (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 2000 - 52nd Annual Conferece on World Affairs (University of Colorado at Boulder); contains participant directory (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 2000 - Beyond Sexual Health Services for Women Who Are Attracted to Women and Men (University of Minnesota); contains brochure (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 2000 - Living Outside the Box: Exploring Gender in the 21st Century (Florida State University); contains program (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 2000 - Midwestern Bisexuality Conference (Metropolitan State University); contains program and schedule (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 2000 - Queer in the Mirror (Stanford University); contains program and conference evaluation form (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 2000 - Trans/forming Gender (Swathmore College); contains program (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 2000 - Y2 Genders (Smith College); contains program (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 2001 - Wisewoman Healing Ways Workshop; contains brochure (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 2002 - Homo-A-Gogo (Olympia, Washington); contains program (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 2002 - Plan Z: A Strategy Conference for Trannies and Wimmin; contains program (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 2002 - Sex and Gender Through Race and Class Working Group Meeting (Barnard College); contains agenda, program, proposal, and notes by Bornstein (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 2003 - Dark Odyssey conference; contains program (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 2004 - Interweave Convocation Weekend; contains packet material (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 2004 - Saying It Loud Conference; contains packet (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 2004 - Transgender 2004, 18th Annual Conference (International Foundation for Gender Education); contains program (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 2005 - Dark Odyssey conference; contains program (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 2005 - FTM: A Gender Odyssey Conference; contains program (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 2005 - Steel City Gender Conference; contains program (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 2006 - Equitiy Forum (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania); contains program (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 2006 - Fresh Fruit: The Fourth International Festival on LGBT Arts and Culture; contains program (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 2007 - Queer Texas Conference; contains program and Bornstein's conference badge noting preferred pronouns, "she/her" (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 2008 - TransOhio Trangender and Ally Symposium; includes corresopndence and keychain (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 2008 - Unity Conference: Are You Being Served? LGBTIQ Representation In the Media; contains program (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 2009 - 9th Annual ISOM Student Gender Conference (University of Mississippi); contais porgram and schedule (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 2009 - Anything But Safe: Sex, Sexuality, and Gender Conference (University of South Florida); contains conference booklet (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 2009 - Gender Odyssey: An International Conference on the Thoughtful Exploration of Gender; contains conference binder material (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 2009 - Northeast LGBT Conference (University of Albany); includes correspondence (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 2009 - Transgender Relious Summit; contains conference binder material (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2010 - Femme 2010 conference (Oakland, California); contains program (Box 5, Folder 2)